Guide to the Howland - Mcintosh Family Papers, 1713-1997 (bulk 1830-1989) RL.00578
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Oversize Materials
  - Shackleford Banks (N.C.) Series
    - Legal Papers Subseries
      - Shackleford Banks, General Abstract Appeals, 85 Civ 1073:
        - Photostat of Title: Division between John Shackleford and Enoch Ward, to Each a 1/2 undivided interest, 1723, Sept. 9 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Title: James Shackleford and John Shackleford to Richard Ward, 1759, June 1 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Title: Division of property between James and John Shackleford at death of their father, John Shackleford, 1736, Mar. 25 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Title: Richard Ward to John Shackleford and James Shackleford, 1759, June1 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Title: James Shackleford to William Fisher, Jr., 1803, Oct. 20 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Deed: James Shackleford to John Shackleford and Roger Shackleford, 1805, Nov. 19 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Deed: Irvin W. Davis, trustee for Carteret County to Mildred W. Holland, 1941, May 27 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Deed: Mabel C. Stephens and husband R. P. Stephens to Mildred W. Holland, 1945, Aug. 22 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Deed: Rosa Davis Chadwick to Corinne C. Uzzell, 1937, Aug. 11 (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Deed: Corinne C. Uzzell to Mabel C. Uzzell, 1953,14 Jan (Box 9)
        - Photostat of Deed: W. F. Howland to W. S. Chadwick, 1895, Jan. 30 (Box 9)
        - Two Photostat Copies of Deed: L. C. Howland, et al. to W. S. Chadwick, 1895, March (Box 9)
        - Genealogy, Court Documents, Title Records; Ralph Howland: Property on Shackleford Banks, General Abstract Appeals: Howland Genealogy, undated[Photocopy and Slide] (Box 9)
        - Genealogy, Court Documents, Title Records; Ralph Howland: Property on Shackleford Banks, General Abstract Appeals: Copy of 1895, Apr. 6Deed, W. F. Howland to W. S. Chadwick (Box 9)
        - Mortgage Deed: Z. J. Howland to William Sabiston, 1886, Apr 4 (Box 9)
        - Warranty Deed: L. C. Howland, Susan P. Howland, Ralph Howland, Alice J. Howland to W. F. Howland, 1894, June 20 (Box 9)
        - Warranty Deed: W. F. Howland to Mary E. Howland, [ 1929?], Apr. 25 (Box 9)
        - Deed of Trust: W. F. Howland and Wife to R. G. Kittrell, Trustee for A. A. C. Co. (American Agricultural Chemical Company), 1932, Jan. 16 (Box 9)
        - Photocopy of Deed of Trust: W. F. Howland and Wife to R. G. Kittrell, Trustee for A. A. C. Co., 1932, Jan. 16 (Box 9)
  - Printed materials Series
    - Woman's World (periodical), 1912, May (Box 9)
    - Campaign poster, Warren G. Harding, 1920 (Box 9)
  - Shackleford Banks (N.C.) Series (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
    - Legal Papers Subseries
      - Map of Shackleford Banks, [1985?] (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Copy of Heirs at Law of Eliza H. Howland, undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Shackleford Banks, General Abstract Appeals, 85 Civ 1703:
        - Record and Statement of Case on Appeal; Geraldine Beveridge et al. vs. William F. Howland, III et al.; Photostats of Deeds marked Ex. 1-Ex.10, 1831-1899[10 items] (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Copy of Heirs at Law of Eliza J. Howland, undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Shackleford Banks, General Abstract Appeals, 85 Civ 1703:
        - Copy of Heirs at Law of Eliza J. Howland, undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Aerial Survey Map of Shackleford Banks; Survey for Warren S. Perry, et al. by Joey Brochure and Associates [Sheet Two], undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Carteret / Superior Court; Court Documents, Correspondence; Photostat of Deed:
        - W. S. Chadwick to W. S. Howland, 1897, Oct. 18 (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Carteret / Superior Court; Court Documents, Correspondence; Genealogy of Land Ownership beginning with John Shackleford and Enoch Ward, Sr., undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Shackleford Banks; General Abstract Appeals; 85 Civ 1703, Title Searches; Ralph Howland:
        - Photostat of Deed: David W. Russell and Wife, Hannah Russell to Simeon Pigott, 1824, Apr. 24 (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Photostat of Deed: Jechonias Pigott to Simeon Pigott et al., 1825, Mar. 20 (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Photostat of Deed: W. S. Chadwick to W. F. Howland, 1897, Oct. 18 (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Survey Map of property of W. S. Chadwick, 1935, May (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Genealogical Materials; Map of Carteret County, Morehead City, Beaufort, Atlantic Beach, Indian Beach, undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Two Aerial Survey Maps; Shackleford Banks, Carteret County, N.C., 1973, Mar. (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Shackleford Banks; General Abstract Appeals; 85 Civ 1703; Survey of the Property of James H. Potter Sr., et al., n. d. (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - McIntosh Family; McIntosh and Sowell Deeds; Warranty Deed: C. P. Jenkins and Wife L. B. Jenkins to M. B. Jenkins, 1883, May 25 (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
      - Legal Papers; Genealogy, Court Documents, Title Records; Ralph Howland:
        - General Abstract Appeals: (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Copy of Heirs at Law of Eliza H. Howland, undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Beveridge File: Copy of Heirs at Law of Eliza J. Howland, undated (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)
        - Property on Shackleford Banks; Beveridge File; Copy of Deed: L. C. Howland and Susan P. Howland, Ralph Howland and Alice S. Howland, Z. J. Howland, Emma J. Howland, W. F. Howland to W. S. Chadwick, 1895, Mar. 12 (Oversize-folder OC:I:4)